export const foodQuiz = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: ` The world's most expensive spice is native to Southwest Asia. What is it? `,
        options: [`Cardamom`, `Vanilla`, `Saffron`, `Star anise`],
        answer: `Saffron`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `What country leads in turkey consumption per person?`,
        options: [`Slovakia`, `Israel`, `Finland`, `United States`],
        answer: `Israel`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `Which country does French toast come from?`,
        options: [`Italy`,`France`, `Germany`, `The Netherlands`],
        answer: `Italy`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `What item is on the table at every Ethiopian meal?`,
        options: [`Steamed rice`, `Injera Bread`, `Curried chickpeas`, `soursop`],
        answer: `Injera Bread`
    }
];

export const animalQuiz = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `What is another name for the sea trout? `,
        options: [`Strongfish`, `Weakfish`, `Fishercrown`, `Rainbowfish`],
        answer: `Weakfish`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `What is the largest cat species on Earth?`,
        options: [`Tiger`, `Lion`, `Leopard`, `Jaguar`],
        answer: `Tiger`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `Which ape is a cousin of the Chimpanzee?`,
        options: [`Mandrill`, `Gorilla`, `Bonobo`, `Orangutan`],
        answer: `Bonobo`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `In what type of animal are offspring hatched by the male?`,
        options: [`koalas`, `squirrels`, `sea cucumbers`, `seahorses`],
        answer: `seahorses`
    }
];

export const geographyQuiz = [
    {
        id: 0,
        question: `Which famous body of water falls on the border between Canada and America? `,
        options: [`Persian Gulf`, `Amazon River`, `Niagara Falls`, `Red Sea`],
        answer: `Niagara Falls`
    },
    {
        id: 1,
        question: `Bangkok is touted as one of the most visited cities in the world. In which Southeast Asian country is this city located?`,
        options: [`Vietnam`, `Laos`, `Philippines`, `Thailand`],
        answer: `Thailand`
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: `The ancient Incan structure called Machu Picchu is located in which South American country?`,
        options: [`Peru`, `Chile`, `Palau`, `Guyana`],
        answer: `Peru`
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: `This African country was infamous in the '80s for having a severe case of drought and famine. Which country is this?`,
        options: [`Egypt`, `Ethiopia`, `Nepal`, `Sudan`],
        answer: `Ethiopia`
    }
];
